♪ Ah, ah, when I was younger ♪
♪ Ah, ah,
should have known better ♪
♪ And I can't feel no remorse ♪
♪ And you don't feel
nothing back ♪
♪ Ah, ah, got a new girlfriend ♪
♪ He feels like he's on top ♪
♪ And I don't feel no remorse ♪
♪ And you can't see past
my blinders ♪
♪ Ophelia, you've been on
my mind, girl, since the flood ♪
♪ Ophelia, heaven help a fool
who falls in love ♪
♪ Ah, ah,
got a little paycheque ♪
♪ You got big plans
and you gotta move ♪
♪ And I don't feel nothing
at all ♪
♪ And you can't feel nothing
small ♪
♪ Honey, I love you,
that's all she wrote ♪
♪ Ophelia, you've been
on my mind, girl, like a drug ♪
♪ Ophelia, heaven help a fool
who falls in love ♪
♪ Ophelia, you've been on
my mind, girl, since the flood ♪
♪ Ophelia, heaven help a fool
who falls in love ♪
♪ Ophelia, you've been on my
mind, girl, like a drug ♪
♪ Ophelia, heaven help a fool
who falls in love ♪
[DISTANT POLICE SIREN]
[♪♪♪]
♪ I was Cleopatra ♪
♪ I was young and an actress ♪
♪ When you knelt by my mattress
and asked for my hand ♪
♪ But I was sad you asked it ♪
♪ As I laid in a black dress ♪
♪ With my father in a casket
I had no plans ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And I left the footprints
the mud stained on the carpet ♪
♪ And it hardened like my
heart did when you left town ♪
♪ But I must admit it ♪
♪ That I would marry you
in an instant ♪
♪ Damn your wife ♪
♪ I'd be your mistress
just to have you around ♪
♪ But I was late for this ♪
♪ Late for that
late for the love of my life ♪
♪ And when I die alone ♪
♪ When I die alone
when I die I'll be on time ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ While the church discouraged ♪
♪ Any lust
that burned within me ♪
♪ Yes, my flesh
it was my currency ♪
♪ But I held true ♪
♪ So I drive a taxi
and the traffic distracts me ♪
♪ From the strangers
in my backseat ♪
♪ They remind me of you ♪
♪ But I was late for this ♪
♪ Late for that ♪
♪ Late for the love of my life ♪
♪ And when I die alone ♪
♪ When I die alone
when I die I'll be on time ♪
♪ And the only gifts
from my Lord ♪
♪ Were a birth and a divorce ♪
♪ But I've read this script
and the costume fits ♪
♪ So I'll play my part ♪
♪ I was Cleopatra ♪
♪ I was taller
than the rafters ♪
♪ But that's all
in the past now ♪
♪ Gone with the wind ♪
♪ Now a nurse in white shoes ♪
♪ Leads me back
to my guestroom ♪
♪ It's a bed and a bathroom ♪
♪ And a place for the end ♪
♪ I won't be late for this ♪
♪ Late for that
late for the love of my life ♪
♪ And when I die alone ♪
♪ When I die alone
when I die I'll be on time ♪
♪ Ah ♪
So sorry...
If we don't leave now,
you may never make it out.
Wait!
OK.
[♪♪♪]
I think that's it.
♪ Pack yourself a toothbrush
dear ♪
♪ Pack yourself
a favourite blouse ♪
♪ Take a withdrawal slip ♪
♪ Take all of your savings out ♪
Can we stop here?
♪ Cause if we don't
leave this town ♪
♪ We might never make it out ♪
♪ I was not born to drown ♪
♪ Baby, come on ♪
♪ Forget what
Father Brennan said ♪
♪ We were not born in sin ♪
♪ Leave a note on your bed ♪
Are you serious?
♪ Let your mother know
you're safe ♪
I'm so tired.
♪ And by the time she wakes ♪
♪ We'll have driven
through the state ♪
through the night ♪
♪ Baby, come on ♪
Heads north, tails south?
- Sure.
Fair enough.
- OK.
♪ If the sun
don't shine on me today ♪
♪ And if the subways flood
and bridges break ♪
♪ Will you lay yourself down
and dig your grave ♪
♪ Or will you rail against
your dying day ♪
♪ And when we looked outside ♪
♪ Couldn't even see the sky ♪
♪ How do you pay the rent
is it your parents? ♪
♪ Or is it hard work, dear ♪
♪ Holding the atmosphere ♪
♪ I don't wanna live like that ♪
♪ If the sun don't shine
on me today ♪
♪ If the subways flood
and the bridges break ♪
Let's get married.
♪ Jesus Christ
can't save me tonight ♪
♪ Put on your dress
yes, wear something nice ♪
♪ Decide on me ♪
♪ Yeah, decide on us ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Illinois, Illinois ♪
♪ Pack yourself a toothbrush
dear ♪
♪ Pack yourself
a favourite blouse ♪
♪ Take a withdrawal slip ♪
♪ Take all of your savings out ♪
♪ Cause if we don't
leave this town ♪
♪ We might never make it out ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ When you left this town ♪
♪ With your windows down ♪
♪ And the wilderness inside ♪
♪ Let the exits pass
all the tar and glass ♪
♪ 'Til the road and sky align ♪
♪ The strangers in this town ♪
♪ They raise you up
just to cut you down ♪
♪ Oh, Angela
it's a long time coming ♪
♪ And your Volvo lights
lit up green and white ♪
♪ With the cities on the signs ♪
♪ But you held your course
to some distant war ♪
♪ In the corners of your mind ♪
♪ From the second time around ♪
♪ The only love I ever found ♪
♪ Oh, Angela
it's a long time coming ♪
♪ Home at last ♪
♪ Were you safe and warm
in your coat of arms ♪
♪ With your fingers in a fist ♪
♪ Did you hear the notes
all those static codes ♪
♪ In the radio abyss? ♪
♪ Strangers in this town ♪
♪ They raise you up
just to cut you down ♪
♪ Oh, Angela
it's a long time coming ♪
♪ Oh, Angela, spent
your whole life running away ♪
♪ Home at last ♪
♪ Vacancy, hotel room ♪
♪ Lost in me, lost in you ♪
♪ Angela, on my knee ♪
♪ I belong, I believe ♪
♪ Home at last ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Oh, the devil's inside ♪
♪ You opened the door ♪
♪ You gave him a ride ♪
♪ Too young to know
too old to admit ♪
♪ That you couldn't see
how it ends ♪
♪ What did you do to my eyes? ♪
♪ What did you sing
to that lonely child? ♪
♪ Promised it all but you lied ♪
♪ You better slow down
baby soon ♪
♪ It's all or nothing to you ♪
♪ The glow of Hollywood signs ♪
♪ They sold you a bridge ♪
♪ They fed you the lines
(Fed you to lions) ♪
♪ You always confused
your servants for friends ♪
♪ But you couldn't see
how it ends ♪
♪ It's all or nothing to you ♪
♪ What did you do to my eyes? ♪
♪ What did you say
to my only child? ♪
♪ Promised your love
but you lied ♪
♪ You better slow down
baby soon ♪
♪ It's all or nothing to you ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ What did you do to my eyes? ♪
♪ What did you sing
to that lonely child? ♪
♪ Promised it all but you lied ♪
♪ You better slow down
baby soon ♪
[♪♪♪]